<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MakeMuscle</string>
    <string name="flatPress">1-Lying flat on bench, hold the dumbbells directly above chest, arms extended.\n\n2-Lower dumbbells to chest in a controlled manner.\n\n3-Press dumbbells back to starting position and repeat.\n\n4-Avoid locking elbows</string>
    <string name="flatChestFly">1-Lying flat on bench, hold dumbbells directly above chest.\n\n2-Bend elbows slightly and maintain throughout the exercise.\n\n3-Open arms to sides. Elbows should remain ‘locked’ in a slightly flexed position.\n\n4-When upper arms are parallel to floor, return the weights to the starting position and repeat.</string>
    <string name="inclineChestPress">1-Adjust bench to an incline of 30 to 45 degrees.\n\n2-Repeat as above.</string>
    <string name="inclineChestFly">1-Adjust bench to an incline of 30 to 45 degrees.\n\n2-Repeat as above.</string>
    <string name="singleRow">1-Stand upright next to bench. Place one knee and hand on bench. Upper body should be parallel to floor.\n\n 2-Hold one dumbbell with arm extended.\n\n3-Raise dumbbell up to your midsection keeping back still throughout movement.\n\n4-Slowly lower dumbbell to start position and repeat. After desired number of reps repeat for other arm.</string>
    <string name="uprightRow">1-Stand upright, feet shoulder width apart, knees slightly bent.\n\n2-Keeping dumbbells close to body, raise them to chin.\n\n3-Hold for a count of 2 and slowly lower to start position and repeat.</string>
    <string name="bentOver">1-Lie face down on a flat or slightly inclined bench.\n\n2-Hold two dumbbells and let arms hang down.Pull dumbbells up towards chest.\n\n3-Slowly lower dumbbells back down and repeat.</string>
    <string name="frontRaise">1-Stand upright, knees slightly bent, shoulder width apart. Palms should be towards thighs.\n\n2-Raise one dumbbell directly in front of you.\n\n3-When arm is parallel to ground lower dumbbell slowly back. Repeat with the other arm.</string>
    <string name="shoulderPress">1-Sit upright on bench with dumbbells over head. Make sure back is flat.\n\n2-Lower dumbbells slowly to shoulders.\n\n3-When arms are at 90 degrees, press the dumbbells back up and repeat.</string>
    <string name="reverseFly">1-Sit on edge of bench, feet flat on the floor. Bend over so chest is almost resting on thighs.\n\n2-Hold dumbbells next to feet and bend arms slightly. Open arms out keeping elbows bent.\n\n3-When arms are parallel to floor, slowly lower dumbbells back.</string>
    <string name="deadLift">1-Stand upright, feet shoulder width apart, knees slightly bent.\n\n2-Bend lower back and knees to lower the weights down your legs. Back must remain flat, lower back should be arched inwards slightly. Keep head up throughout exercise.\n\n3-Stand upright using lower back and legs, maintaining flat back and keeping your head up.</string>
    <string name="lungs">1-Holding dumbbells at sides, stand upright with feet slightly less than shoulder width apart.\n\n2-Step forward about 2 feet with one foot and bend knee to about 90 degrees. As you plant your foot bend trailing knee so it nearly touches floor.\n\n3-Push off with front foot to return to starting position.\n\n4-Repeat for the desired number of reps and change legs.</string>
    <string name="french">1-Lie flat on bench. Hold dumbbells directly above chest with palms facing each other. Dumbbells should be just about touching each other.\n\n2-Keeping your shoulders locked, let your elbows fold so dumbbells are lowered down to either side of head.\n\n3-Extend both your arms back to start position and repeat.</string>
    <string name="squats">1-Holding dumbbells at sides, stand upright with your feet shoulder width apart.\n\n2-Bend from knees until thighs are almost parallel to the ground (avoid letting knees turn inwards).\n\n3-Keep back flat, lower back slightly arched inwards and head up.\n\n4-Return to upright position and repeat.</string>
    <string name="hammer">1-Stand upright with dumbells at sides.\n\n2-Turn palms inward so they face body.\n\n3-Curl dumbbells up slowly keeping your elbows close to sides.</string>
    <string name="overheadTriceps">1-Stand upright, feet shoulder width apart.\n\n2-Hold dumbbell directly above head with arm fully extended. Clasp elbow with free hand for support.\n\n3-Slowly let elbow fold so dumbbell is lowered behind head.\n\n4-Extend arm back to starting position. Repeat for the desired number of reps and switch arms.</string>
    <string name="declineBicep">1-Adjust bench to a 45 degree incline.\n\n2-Hold dumbbells at sides. Arms should be fully extended.\n\n3-Keep elbows close to body and curl weight up by bending elblows.\n\n4-Slowly lower dumbbells and repeat.</string>
    <string name="tip2">When it comes to nutrition, consider these nutritional goals:\n\nConsume enough calories from carbohydrates through foods and beverages high in carbs.\n\nEat enough to prevent hunger. Concentrate on easily digested, high-quality carbohydrates such as bananas, grapes, watermelon, dates and peaches, and foods with low-to-moderate protein content, fiber and fat to prevent digestive issues.\n\nDrink adequate fluids and electrolytes.</string>
</resources>


